



Jakub Jurkiewicz

E-mail: jakubxjurkiewicz@gmail.com
Phone: 514 154 689

1 11011C. **314 134 003**

Date of birth: 16.09.1998 City: Olsztyn

Frontend Developer with more than 2 years of commercial experience. Software development is my passion. My current goal is to continue my professional development, expand my knowledge, gain skills both technical and soft. For the past six months, I have been learning the React library, in which I have so far completed several non-commercial projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

06.2021 - 07.2023 (2 years 2 months)

• Frontend Developer | Redicon - Software House | Olsztyn

Brief job description:

Creating responsive applications, implementing the front-end based on a graphic template, integrating and configuring CMS. Through this, I have acquired skills in HTML, CSS (including SASS, TailwindCSS, Bootstrap), JS, jQuery, PHP, working with a MySQL database, API integration, proficiency in using Photoshop, Figma, Adobe XD, Avocode, project management through Jira, Redmine, and GIT.

Support for Wordpress, Woocommerce, many popular plugins like ACF, Contact Form 7, plugin development, SEO optimization.

punkta.pl

Platform for selling insurance. Creation of new functionalities based on JavaScript, IT support, integration with CMS, LP, promotional actions.

Rumszewicz Sailing

Online store offering sailing camps for children and teenagers. Implementation of a graphic template, integration with CMS, proprietary solutions for managing participants, assigning to rooms.

worwo.pro

Online store selling vacuum cleaner bags and accessories. Store management, bag scanner, testing and optimization.

09.2016 - 10.2016 (2 months)

• Intern | Redicon - Software House | Olsztyn

Brief job description:

Internship at a high school. Learning the basics of HTML, CSS and Javascript.

EDUCATION

09.2014 - 06.2018 (3 years 10 months)

• Zespół Szkół Ekonomicznych im. Mikołaja Kopernika w Olsztynie

Specialization: IT Specialist

LANGUAGE SKILLS

English: advanced **Polish:** native

SKILLS

 $HTML5 \cdot CSS3 \cdot SASS \cdot JavaScript \cdot RWD \cdot Linux \cdot PHP \cdot MySQL \cdot Git \cdot React.js \cdot jQuery \cdot TailwindCSS \cdot Bootstrap \cdot WordPress \cdot Node.js \cdot SEO \cdot Next.js$

COURSES, CERTIFICATES

11.2018

• Search engines: website positioning and optimization

Host: ProcessTeam

11.2018

• Managing Google Apps for Work - G Suite

Host: ProcessTeam

10.2018

• Project management "Session" - part II.

Host: ProcessTeam

08.2018

• Qualification E.14 Web and database application development and administration

10.2017

• Geoinformatics systems in practice with field data acquisition and processing Host: VCC

08.2017

• Qualification E.13 Design of local area networks and network administration

08.2016

• Qualification E.12 Assembly and operation of personal computers and peripheral devices

HOBBIES

automotive, personal development, mixed martial arts

LINKS

Github

https://github.com/jxjurkiewicz

Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jakub-jurkiewicz-970723286/